Rinkham,
do you know what the people in town are saying about you?
Let them talk.
It is no small matter.
You are far too close with Kaew.
Whomever I am close with is my own business.
No, it is not, not as long as you are my child.
Then what am I? Merely a tool for you, Dad?
You do not understand.
I understand completely.
You are controlling my life to suit your own desires.
Regardless, you must marry Khun Chai Phakdee.
If he can put up with me, let him try.
It looks beautiful.
Make plenty of it.
Yes, Lady.
Lady Rinkham.
Today, I will take you out.
I am not going.
But we are about to be engaged.
We are not engaged yet, do not be so hasty.
Kaew, I want some sweets.
Feed me, Kaew.
I told you to do it.
Hey, you don't need to let the caretaker do everything like this.
I am content with this.
Or are you dissatisfied?
Kaew, fix my hair for me, please.
Hey, I think we should talk in private.
I am not free.
I am sleepy now.
No matter who it is, do not disturb me.
You shouldn't speak like that in front of others.
I just wanted him to see that I have made my choice.
But you are putting yourself at risk.
I am not afraid.
Or is it you who is scared?
Then prove it to me.
I only want you to be careful with your words and actions.
It might cause…
And what about you?
What should you be careful of?
I should be careful of you, Rinkham.
It's broad daylight,
and the house is full of people.
You shouldn’t…
Then don't make a sound.
You just have to endure it, that's all.
Dad
Dad..
Please sit up
and take your medicine.
Help…
Okay
Let me help you.
How are you doing, Kaew?
Are you tired?
I'm not tired.
I'm used to it.
Someone’s coming…
What is the meaning of this, you all?
Lord Wisanu…
I have no issue with you being in love with Rinkham.
But I just found out something from someone,
so I came to prove it.
You are a woman!
You deceived me!
Please let me explain.
Enough!
From now on, Rinkham will be entering the engagement ceremony with Khun Chai Phakdee.
She has someone else to protect her in your place now.
Therefore, you must leave my house.
Get out of my daughter's life,
and never let me see your face again.
Please let me explain.
I don't want to hear it.
From this moment on, you are no longer a citizen of my town.
I give you only one month
to get out of this town.
Otherwise, don't say I didn't warn you.
Kaew.
Dad.
What on earth happened, my child?
I just wanted to get money to cure your illness.
I just wanted you to get better,
so that we could have a better life.
That’s why I disguised myself as a man,
thinking I could keep everything under control.
But I was wrong.
I disappointed the people I love
and brought trouble to everyone.
I’m so sorry.
Do you love her?
I love her with all my heart.
If you truly love her,
that love will bring you back together.
I used to believe in fate…
but now, I’m not so sure.
Where is Kaew?
Why are you so late today?
Don't waste your time waiting for her.
I’ve banished her from the city
and he better never show her face around here again.
What?!
He isn't fit to be anywhere near you.
What have you done? Why...?
You know full well in your heart why I drove her away.
She lied.
You lied.
You aren't the only one who knows
that Kaewket is actually a woman.
I hate you, Dad!
But I love you.
I only want what's best for you.
Love?
What about my love?
Have you ever thought about that at all?!
From now on, you will be engaged to Khun Chai Phakdee.
And it must happen as soon as possible.